Gabriele Medeot

I am a Machine Learning Researcher and Software Engineer specialising in deep learning and generative models. I am able to build machine learning models extremely rapidly, and move them swiftly from prototype to production. I'm a fast learner and acquire new knowledge easily. I am also a musician, playing wind

(+44) 07762246782 ghaelen.m@gmail.com

SELECTED WORKING EXPERIENCE

instruments: clarinet, saxophone and flute.

Jukedeck, London (UK) — *Machine Learning Researcher*

APRIL 2015 - PRESENT

At Jukedeck we do cutting edge research in the field of music generation with deep learning. The company has been featured in BBC, The Financial Times, The New York Times, Wired and Forbes and won prizes like Techcrunch, Le Web, and the Cannes Lions innovation award. I brought machine learning to Jukedeck four years ago, and since then helped to build the team via helping out the hiring. At the moment I develop machine learning prototypes, research new models and also manage a Junior Machine Learning Researcher

Smartlab University of Trieste, Trieste (IT) — *Internship*

OCTOBER 2011 - APRIL 2012

At SmartLab of the University of Trieste I worked on installing laser and ultrasound sensors on a self driving wheeled robot.

Lionello Stock Middle School, Trieste (IT) — *Clarinet Teacher*

JUNE 2011 - JULY 2011

I was a supply teacher at the Lionello Stock Middle School of Trieste for one month, teaching music theory and clarinet performance.

EDUCATION

La Sapienza University, Rome (IT) — *Master's Degree in Artificial Intelligence and Robotics* October 2012 - APRIL 2015 - GRADE 110/100

I learnt to design and implement artificial intelligence and robotic systems, as well as the interdisciplinary skills that are essential to managing complex projects and their impact on the society.

University of Trieste, Trieste (IT) — *Bachelor's Degree in Software Engineering* October 2007 - APRIL 2012

I learnt all the skills required to design software in most programming languages as well as manage complex projects from beginning to the end.

Conservatory of Trieste, Trieste (IT) — *Bachelor's Degree in Clarinet Performance* JULY 2010

Here I studied clarinet performance to the professional level, and acquired the skills needed to play clarinet in orchestra and chamber music ensembles and teach music theory and clarinet performance.

PUBLICATIONS

StrucutureNet: Inducing Structure in Generated Melodies

The 19th International Society of Music Information Retrieval Conference 2018 http://ismir2018.ircam.fr/doc/pdfs/126_Paper.pdf

SKILLS

Artificial Intelligence

Machine Learning

Deep Learning

Reinforcement

Learning

Generative Models

Recurrent Models

Python,

Tensorflow, Theano

Keras

Matlab, octave

Java, c++

HTML, PHP, CSS

LANGUAGES

Italian

Mother Tongue

English

Full Working

Proficiency

Spanish

Limited Working

Proficiency

Chinese

Elementary Proficiency

Japanese

Elementary Proficiency